<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Juan Osorio]]></title><description><![CDATA[Juan Osorio]]></description><link>https://juanosorio94.github.io</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 15:32:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><item><title><![CDATA[What is Syzkaller, how does it work?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Syzkaller In this entry I want to outline the main points of 
Syzkaller, a program which fuzzes the linux kernel by generating
programs that…]]></description><link>https://juanosorio94.github.io/Syzkaller/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://juanosorio94.github.io/Syzkaller/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 21:44:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h1&gt;Syzkaller&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this entry I want to outline the main points of
Syzkaller, a program which fuzzes the linux kernel by generating
programs that execute system calls.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Just for learning purposses, I wanted to fit as much relevant
information (in my ignorant opinion) about syzkaller as possible
into one blog post. Coherence is not guaranteed ;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Goal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Find bugs inside kernel (not restricted to linux).
In order to achieve this, syzkaller starts a defined
amount of VMs, in which the kernel is continously
fuzzed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Running Syzkaller&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the main entry point of syzkaller is a program called
syz-manager, which is responsible for managing
the virtual machines. It also starts an http server which
serves a dashboard with information about crashes,
code coverage, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;How Syzkaller works&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Syz-manager starts, monitors and restarts several VM instances, and
starts a syz-fuzzer process inside of the VMs. The Syz-manager is
responsible for persistent corpus and crash storage, it runs on a
host with a stable kernel which does not experiecne white-noise
fuzzer load.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://github.com/google/syzkaller/blob/master/docs/process_structure.png?raw=true&quot; alt=&quot;Syzkaller Architecture&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The syz-fuzzer is the process that runs inside the VMs (whose kernel
are the fuzzing target). The syz-fuzzer guides the fuzzing process
(generates inout, mutates and minimizes, among other things)  and
sends input that triggers new coverage via RPC to the syz-manager.
Syz-fuzzer also starts syz-executor processes, which are in charge
of actually executing the programs generated by syz-fuzzer, and then
terminate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;each syz-executor executes a sequence of system calls, which are
given by the syz-fuzzer process, and then sends the results back
to syz-fuzzer. It is written in C++, and designed to be as simple
as possible, so it does not interfere with the fuzzing at all. It is
compiled as a static binary and commmunicates with syz-fuzzer using
shared memory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Syzkaller VMs&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There are some generic requirements of a Syzkaller VM:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Networking support, because the fuzzing processes
communicate with the outside world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SSH Server, as program files for the fuzzer processes
are transmitted into the VM using SSH.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SSH config should be set to allow root access.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A mounted debugfs filesystem, as the kernel
exports coverage information via a debugfs entry. (See KCOV)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;as I am interested in fuzzing a specific device driver inside
the linux kernel, I compiled it with all the required instrumentation
(KASAN, KCOV, etc) and also compiled the drivers im interested in as modules&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;in my case, for the software impl of RoCE (RDMA over
Converged Ethernet) rdma_rxe, a character device file is
exposed /dev/infiniband/uverbs after creating a software rdma device,
this is achieved right after login by executing a shell script (using
the .bashrc file)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Program generation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Syzkaller uses its own language to describe system calls. Because
depending on its use and context, the same system call may provide
a very different function, the need to describe this behaviour
gave entrance to syzkallers system call description language,
syzlang.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;inside syzkaller’s source tree, this definitions are found
inside /sys/[operatingsystem]/*.txt files.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A program is a sequence of syscalls with concrete values for
arguments.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Programs passed to syz-executor are in binary represenation, they
are actually interpreted by /prog/decodeexec.go&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Syzlang&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A “Pseudo-formal” grammar used to describe syscalls:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;text&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;syscallname &amp;quot;(&amp;quot; [arg [&amp;quot;,&amp;quot; arg]*] &amp;quot;)&amp;quot; [type] [&amp;quot;(&amp;quot; attribute* &amp;quot;)&amp;quot;]
arg = argname type
argname = identifier
type = typename [ &amp;quot;[&amp;quot; type-options &amp;quot;]&amp;quot; ]
typename = &amp;quot;const&amp;quot; | &amp;quot;intN&amp;quot; | &amp;quot;intptr&amp;quot; | &amp;quot;flags&amp;quot; | &amp;quot;array&amp;quot; | &amp;quot;ptr&amp;quot; |
	   &amp;quot;string&amp;quot; | &amp;quot;strconst&amp;quot; | &amp;quot;filename&amp;quot; | &amp;quot;len&amp;quot; |
	   &amp;quot;bytesize&amp;quot; | &amp;quot;bytesizeN&amp;quot; | &amp;quot;bitsize&amp;quot; | &amp;quot;vma&amp;quot; | &amp;quot;proc&amp;quot;
type-options = [type-opt [&amp;quot;,&amp;quot; type-opt]]&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Crashes&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once a crash is detected in one of the VMs, Syzkaller
will start the process of reproducing the crash and
then minimize the program that causes it. VMs will
stop fuzzing in order to reproduce detected crashes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Crash logs are stored inside a directory called
workdir/crashes, it contains the progams that
were executed just before a crash occured.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Syzkaller programs are generated by a set of system
calls defined by a language called Syzlang, These
can also be locally executed by syz-execprog and
translated into c with syz-prog2c.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the process of finding a crash reprodution is
“automated to some degree” with another
tool inside syzkaller, called syz-repro.
In order to run syz-repro, pass the syzmanager
config file and the crsah report file.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Compilers introduction]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Goal of the Compiler The goal of a compiler is just to take a source code as an input and translate it into
a target machine code (e.g…]]></description><link>https://juanosorio94.github.io/compilers-1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://juanosorio94.github.io/compilers-1/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 21:44:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;The Goal of the Compiler&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The goal of a compiler is just to take a source code as an input and translate it into
a target machine code (e.g. x86 Assembly), which is not even yet the object code that
gets executed on the cpu. After compiling, the assembler and the linker take care of
that task.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Compiler phases&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In order to achieve its goal, compilers have been designed into phases, One great benefit
about doing this is that we get a lot of modularity. We can create new compilers
by interchanging reusable modules.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Phase 1: Lexical Analysis&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;the first phase when a program is fed to a compiler is
analysing the stream of characters and groupping them
into meaningful sequences called lexemes. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;for each of the lexemes, the lexical analyzer produces tokens as
outputs (passed further down to the next step: syntax analysis),
roupping them as (token name, attribute value), where the
token name is an abstract symbol that is used during syntax analysis,
the attribute value points to an entry in the symbol table for this
token. Information from the symbol table entry is needed for semantic
analysis and code generation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some tokens do not need attribute values to identify them inside
the symbol table, e.g. the equals sign in an assignment. the variable,
however, could produce something like (id, 2), the equals sign (=, _)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Syntax Analysis&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The syntax analysis, also known as parsing, is the second phase of the
compiler in which it uses the output from the first phase (tokens)
to create a tree like intermediate representation that corresponds to
the grammatical structure of the token stream. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Semantic Analysis&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The semantic analyzer takes the output from the previous step and also
the information from the symbol table (this is present in all steps),
and checks against the language definition for semantic consistency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Type information is also gathered and stored inside the symbol table
or inside the syntax tree. Type checking is also part of the semantic
analysis, where the compiler checks that each operator has matching
operands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Intermediate Code Generation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Code Optimization&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Code Generation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Symbol Table Management&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The compiler records variable names found in the source program and
collects information about various attributes of each name -for instance,
information about the allocated storeage for a name, its type, scope,
and in case of procedures, number and types of arguments, the method of
passing the arguments, and the type returned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Compiler Construction Tools&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parser generators: produce syntax analyzers from a
grammatical description of a language.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scanner generators: produce lexical analyzers from a regular-expression
description of the tokens of a language.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Syntax-directed translation engines: produce a collection of routines
for walking a parse tree and generating intermediate code.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Code-generators generators: produce code generators from a collection
of rules for translating each operation of the intermediate language into
the the machine language for a target machine.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Data-flow analysis engines: facilitate the gathering of information
about how values are transmitted from one part of a program to each other
part. Data-flow analysis is a key part of code optimization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Compiler-construction toolkits that provide an integrated set of
routines for constructing various phases of a compiler.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Context Free Grammars&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Used to specify the syntax of a language, a context free grammar has four
components:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A set of terminal symbols, also referred as tokens, they are the
elementary symbols of the language defined by the grammar.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A set of nonterminals, sometimes called “syntactic variables”,
each nonterminal represents a set of string of terminals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A set of productions, where each one consists of a nonterminal, called
the head or left side of the production, an arrow and a sequence of
terminals and/or nonterminals, called the body or right side of the
production&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A designation of one of the nonterminals as the start symbol.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Parsing&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parsing is the problem of taking a string of terminals and figuring out how
to derive it from the start symbol of the grammar and if it cannot be
derived from the start symbol of the grammar, then reporting syntax errors
within the string.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Ambiguity&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A grammar can have more than one parsing tree generating a given string of
terminals, such a grammar is said to be ambiguous. To show that a grammar
is ambiguous, it suffices to find a terminal string that can yield more than
one parsing tree.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Associtivity of operators&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When an operand in a mathematical expression sits in the middle, e.g. 5 in
4 - 5 + 6, we need to stick to a convention to help us decide the outcome
of the math expression. In most programming languages, the four common
mathematical operators are &lt;em&gt;left associative&lt;/em&gt; meaning that an operand within
to plus signs for example belongs to the operator on the left.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Operators like exponentiation are right associative, as well as the the
assignment operator we see in languages like C.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Parse trees for left associative grammars grow (nest) towards the left,
while in right associative grammars, they grow (nest) towards the right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a great hint is given, by which which of the non terminal symbols can be
expanded (most likely in some kind of a recursive fashion) for a given
production. If its the one on the right, there is a high likelihood it is
a right associative grammar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Operators can also have precedence. We say an operator has higher precendence
than another operator if it takes it operands before the one with the lower
precedence does (* takes for example its operands before + does).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;excerpt from book about grammars that implement precedence level:
We can generalize this idea to any number of n precedence levels.
We need n+1 nonterminals. The first (highest precedence) can never be torn
apart. Typically, the production bodies for this nonterminal are only single
operands and parenthesized expressions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Syntax directed translation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Syntax directed translation is done by attaching rules or program fragments
to productions in a grammar. &lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Syntax Highlighting Post]]></title><description><![CDATA[Syntax highlighting is a feature that displays source code, in different colors and fonts according to the category of terms. This feature…]]></description><link>https://juanosorio94.github.io/code-highlighting-post/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://juanosorio94.github.io/code-highlighting-post/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 07:26:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Syntax highlighting is a feature that displays source code, in different colors and fonts according to the category of terms. This feature facilitates writing in a structured language such as a programming language or a markup language as both structures and syntax errors are visually distinct. Highlighting does not affect the meaning of the text itself; it is intended only for human readers.&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref-1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn-1&quot; class=&quot;footnote-ref&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Fenced Code Blocks&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;gatsby-highlight&quot; data-language=&quot;css&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;language-css&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-css&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token selector&quot;&gt;#container&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;token property&quot;&gt;float&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; left&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;token property&quot;&gt;margin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; 0 -240px 0 0&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;token property&quot;&gt;width&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; 100%&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li id=&quot;fn-1&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Syntax_highlighting&quot;&gt;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Syntax_highlighting&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;#fnref-1&quot; class=&quot;footnote-backref&quot;&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sample Link Post]]></title><description><![CDATA[This theme supports link posts, made famous by John Gruber. To use, just add  to the post’s YAML front matter and you’re done. And this is…]]></description><link>https://juanosorio94.github.io/sample-link-post/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://juanosorio94.github.io/sample-link-post/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 07:26:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This theme supports &lt;strong&gt;link posts&lt;/strong&gt;, made famous by John Gruber. To use, just add &lt;code class=&quot;language-text&quot;&gt;link: http://url-you-want-linked&lt;/code&gt; to the post’s YAML front matter and you’re done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And this is how a quote looks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some &lt;a href=&quot;http://renyuanz.github.io&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt; can also be shown.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Testing "Readability" with a Bunch of Text]]></title><description><![CDATA[Portland in shoreditch Vice, labore typewriter pariatur hoodie fap sartorial Austin. Pinterest literally occupy Schlitz forage. Odio ad blue…]]></description><link>https://juanosorio94.github.io/readability-post/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://juanosorio94.github.io/readability-post/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 07:26:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;Portland in shoreditch Vice, labore typewriter pariatur hoodie fap sartorial Austin. Pinterest literally occupy Schlitz forage. Odio ad blue bottle vinyl, 90’s narwhal commodo bitters pour-over nostrud. Ugh est hashtag in, fingerstache adipisicing laboris esse Pinterest shabby chic Portland. Shoreditch bicycle rights anim, flexitarian laboris put a bird on it vinyl cupidatat narwhal. Hashtag artisan skateboard, flannel Bushwick nesciunt salvia aute fixie do plaid post-ironic dolor McSweeney’s. Cliche pour-over chambray nulla four loko skateboard sapiente hashtag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vero laborum commodo occupy. Semiotics voluptate mumblecore pug. Cosby sweater ullamco quinoa ennui assumenda, sapiente occupy delectus lo-fi. Ea fashion axe Marfa cillum aliquip. Retro Bushwick keytar cliche. Before they sold out sustainable gastropub Marfa readymade, ethical Williamsburg skateboard brunch qui consectetur gentrify semiotics. Mustache cillum irony, fingerstache magna pour-over keffiyeh tousled selfies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Cupidatat 90’s lo-fi authentic try-hard&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In pug Portland incididunt mlkshk put a bird on it vinyl quinoa. Terry Richardson shabby chic +1, scenester Tonx excepteur tempor fugiat voluptate fingerstache aliquip nisi next level. Farm-to-table hashtag Truffaut, Odd Future ex meggings gentrify single-origin coffee try-hard 90’s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sartorial hoodie&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Labore viral forage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tote bag selvage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DIY exercitation et id ugh tumblr church-key&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Incididunt umami sriracha, ethical fugiat VHS ex assumenda yr irure direct trade. Marfa Truffaut bicycle rights, kitsch placeat Etsy kogi asymmetrical. Beard locavore flexitarian, kitsch photo booth hoodie plaid ethical readymade leggings yr.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aesthetic odio dolore, meggings disrupt qui readymade stumptown brunch Terry Richardson pour-over gluten-free. Banksy american apparel in selfies, biodiesel flexitarian organic meh wolf quinoa gentrify banjo kogi. Readymade tofu ex, scenester dolor umami fingerstache occaecat fashion axe Carles jean shorts minim. Keffiyeh fashion axe nisi Godard mlkshk dolore. Lomo you probably haven’t heard of them eu non, Odd Future Truffaut pug keytar meggings McSweeney’s Pinterest cred. Etsy literally aute esse, eu bicycle rights qui meggings fanny pack. Gentrify leggings pug flannel duis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Forage occaecat cardigan qui&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fashion axe hella gastropub lo-fi kogi 90’s aliquip +1 veniam delectus tousled. Cred sriracha locavore gastropub kale chips, iPhone mollit sartorial. Anim dolore 8-bit, pork belly dolor photo booth aute flannel small batch. Dolor disrupt ennui, tattooed whatever salvia Banksy sartorial roof party selfies raw denim sint meh pour-over. Ennui eu cardigan sint, gentrify iPhone cornhole.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whatever velit occaecat quis deserunt gastropub, leggings elit tousled roof party 3 wolf moon kogi pug blue bottle ea. Fashion axe shabby chic Austin quinoa pickled laborum bitters next level, disrupt deep v accusamus non fingerstache.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tote bag asymmetrical elit sunt. Occaecat authentic Marfa, hella McSweeney’s next level irure veniam master cleanse. Sed hoodie letterpress artisan wolf leggings, 3 wolf moon commodo ullamco. Anim occupy ea labore Terry Richardson. Tofu ex master cleanse in whatever pitchfork banh mi, occupy fugiat fanny pack Austin authentic. Magna fugiat 3 wolf moon, labore McSweeney’s sustainable vero consectetur. Gluten-free disrupt enim, aesthetic fugiat jean shorts trust fund keffiyeh magna try-hard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Hoodie Duis&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Actually salvia consectetur, hoodie duis lomo YOLO sunt sriracha. Aute pop-up brunch farm-to-table odio, salvia irure occaecat. Sriracha small batch literally skateboard. Echo Park nihil hoodie, aliquip forage artisan laboris. Trust fund reprehenderit nulla locavore. Stumptown raw denim kitsch, keffiyeh nulla twee dreamcatcher fanny pack ullamco 90’s pop-up est culpa farm-to-table. Selfies 8-bit do pug odio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Thundercats Ho!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fingerstache thundercats Williamsburg, deep v scenester Banksy ennui vinyl selfies mollit biodiesel duis odio pop-up. Banksy 3 wolf moon try-hard, sapiente enim stumptown deep v ad letterpress. Squid beard brunch, exercitation raw denim yr sint direct trade. Raw denim narwhal id, flannel DIY McSweeney’s seitan. Letterpress artisan bespoke accusamus, meggings laboris consequat Truffaut qui in seitan. Sustainable cornhole Schlitz, twee Cosby sweater banh mi deep v forage letterpress flannel whatever keffiyeh. Sartorial cred irure, semiotics ethical sed blue bottle nihil letterpress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Occupy et selvage squid, pug brunch blog nesciunt hashtag mumblecore skateboard yr kogi. Ugh small batch swag four loko. Fap post-ironic qui tote bag farm-to-table american apparel scenester keffiyeh vero, swag non pour-over gentrify authentic pitchfork. Schlitz scenester lo-fi voluptate, tote bag irony bicycle rights pariatur vero Vice freegan wayfarers exercitation nisi shoreditch. Chambray tofu vero sed. Street art swag literally leggings, Cosby sweater mixtape PBR lomo Banksy non in pitchfork ennui McSweeney’s selfies. Odd Future Banksy non authentic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aliquip enim artisan dolor post-ironic. Pug tote bag Marfa, deserunt pour-over Portland wolf eu odio intelligentsia american apparel ugh ea. Sunt viral et, 3 wolf moon gastropub pug id. Id fashion axe est typewriter, mlkshk Portland art party aute brunch. Sint pork belly Cosby sweater, deep v mumblecore kitsch american apparel. Try-hard direct trade tumblr sint skateboard. Adipisicing bitters excepteur biodiesel, pickled gastropub aute veniam.&lt;/p&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sample Post]]></title><description><![CDATA[HTML Elements Below is just about everything you’ll need to style in the theme. Check the source code to see the many embedded elements…]]></description><link>https://juanosorio94.github.io/sample-post-1/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://juanosorio94.github.io/sample-post-1/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 07:26:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;HTML Elements&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is just about everything you’ll need to style in the theme. Check the source code to see the many embedded elements within paragraphs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Heading 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Heading 2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Heading 3&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Heading 4&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Heading 5&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;Heading 6&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Body text&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, test link adipiscing elit. &lt;strong&gt;This is strong&lt;/strong&gt;. Nullam dignissim convallis est. Quisque aliquam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1440635592348-167b1b30296f?crop=entropy&amp;#x26;dpr=2&amp;#x26;fit=crop&amp;#x26;fm=jpg&amp;#x26;h=475&amp;#x26;ixjsv=2.1.0&amp;#x26;ixlib=rb-0.3.5&amp;#x26;q=50&amp;#x26;w=1250&quot; alt=&quot;Smithsonian Image&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is emphasized&lt;/em&gt;. Donec faucibus. Nunc iaculis suscipit dui. 53 = 125. Water is H2O. Nam sit amet sem. Aliquam libero nisi, imperdiet at, tincidunt nec, gravida vehicula, nisl. The New York Times (That’s a citation). Underline.Maecenas ornare tortor. Donec sed tellus eget sapien fringilla nonummy. Mauris a ante. Suspendisse quam sem, consequat at, commodo vitae, feugiat in, nunc. Morbi imperdiet augue quis tellus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HTML and CSS are our tools. Mauris a ante. Suspendisse quam sem, consequat at, commodo vitae, feugiat in, nunc. Morbi imperdiet augue quis tellus. Praesent mattis, massa quis luctus fermentum, turpis mi volutpat justo, eu volutpat enim diam eget metus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Blockquotes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, test link adipiscing elit. Nullam dignissim convallis est. Quisque aliquam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Tables&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Header 1&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;Header 2&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;Header 3&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;cell 1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;cell 2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;cell 3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;cell 4&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;cell 5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;cell 6&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;List Types&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Ordered Lists&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Item one&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sub item one&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sub item two&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sub item three&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item two&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Unordered Lists&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item one&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item two&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item three&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Post with Large Feature Image and Text]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is a sample post with a large feature image up top and tons of text. Odio ad blue bottle vinyl, 90’s narwhal commodo bitters pour-over…]]></description><link>https://juanosorio94.github.io/readability-feature-post/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://juanosorio94.github.io/readability-feature-post/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 07:26:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;p&gt;This is a sample post with a large feature image&lt;sup id=&quot;fnref-1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#fn-1&quot; class=&quot;footnote-ref&quot;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; up top and tons of text. Odio ad blue bottle vinyl, 90’s narwhal commodo bitters pour-over nostrud. Ugh est hashtag in, fingerstache adipisicing laboris esse Pinterest shabby chic Portland. Shoreditch bicycle rights anim, flexitarian laboris put a bird on it vinyl cupidatat narwhal. Hashtag artisan skateboard, flannel Bushwick nesciunt salvia aute fixie do plaid post-ironic dolor McSweeney’s. Cliche pour-over chambray nulla four loko skateboard sapiente hashtag.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Vero laborum commodo occupy. Semiotics voluptate mumblecore pug. Cosby sweater ullamco quinoa ennui assumenda, sapiente occupy delectus lo-fi. Ea fashion axe Marfa cillum aliquip. Retro Bushwick keytar cliche. Before they sold out sustainable gastropub Marfa readymade, ethical Williamsburg skateboard brunch qui consectetur gentrify semiotics. Mustache cillum irony, fingerstache magna pour-over keffiyeh tousled selfies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Cupidatat 90’s lo-fi authentic try-hard&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In pug Portland incididunt mlkshk put a bird on it vinyl quinoa. Terry Richardson shabby chic +1, scenester Tonx excepteur tempor fugiat voluptate fingerstache aliquip nisi next level. Farm-to-table hashtag Truffaut, Odd Future ex meggings gentrify single-origin coffee try-hard 90’s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sartorial hoodie&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Labore viral forage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tote bag selvage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;DIY exercitation et id ugh tumblr church-key&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Incididunt umami sriracha, ethical fugiat VHS ex assumenda yr irure direct trade. Marfa Truffaut bicycle rights, kitsch placeat Etsy kogi asymmetrical. Beard locavore flexitarian, kitsch photo booth hoodie plaid ethical readymade leggings yr.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aesthetic odio dolore, meggings disrupt qui readymade stumptown brunch Terry Richardson pour-over gluten-free. Banksy american apparel in selfies, biodiesel flexitarian organic meh wolf quinoa gentrify banjo kogi. Readymade tofu ex, scenester dolor umami fingerstache occaecat fashion axe Carles jean shorts minim. Keffiyeh fashion axe nisi Godard mlkshk dolore. Lomo you probably haven’t heard of them eu non, Odd Future Truffaut pug keytar meggings McSweeney’s Pinterest cred. Etsy literally aute esse, eu bicycle rights qui meggings fanny pack. Gentrify leggings pug flannel duis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Forage occaecat cardigan qui&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fashion axe hella gastropub lo-fi kogi 90’s aliquip +1 veniam delectus tousled. Cred sriracha locavore gastropub kale chips, iPhone mollit sartorial. Anim dolore 8-bit, pork belly dolor photo booth aute flannel small batch. Dolor disrupt ennui, tattooed whatever salvia Banksy sartorial roof party selfies raw denim sint meh pour-over. Ennui eu cardigan sint, gentrify iPhone cornhole.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Whatever velit occaecat quis deserunt gastropub, leggings elit tousled roof party 3 wolf moon kogi pug blue bottle ea. Fashion axe shabby chic Austin quinoa pickled laborum bitters next level, disrupt deep v accusamus non fingerstache.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tote bag asymmetrical elit sunt. Occaecat authentic Marfa, hella McSweeney’s next level irure veniam master cleanse. Sed hoodie letterpress artisan wolf leggings, 3 wolf moon commodo ullamco. Anim occupy ea labore Terry Richardson. Tofu ex master cleanse in whatever pitchfork banh mi, occupy fugiat fanny pack Austin authentic. Magna fugiat 3 wolf moon, labore McSweeney’s sustainable vero consectetur. Gluten-free disrupt enim, aesthetic fugiat jean shorts trust fund keffiyeh magna try-hard.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Hoodie Duis&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Actually salvia consectetur, hoodie duis lomo YOLO sunt sriracha. Aute pop-up brunch farm-to-table odio, salvia irure occaecat. Sriracha small batch literally skateboard. Echo Park nihil hoodie, aliquip forage artisan laboris. Trust fund reprehenderit nulla locavore. Stumptown raw denim kitsch, keffiyeh nulla twee dreamcatcher fanny pack ullamco 90’s pop-up est culpa farm-to-table. Selfies 8-bit do pug odio.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Thundercats Ho!&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Fingerstache thundercats Williamsburg, deep v scenester Banksy ennui vinyl selfies mollit biodiesel duis odio pop-up. Banksy 3 wolf moon try-hard, sapiente enim stumptown deep v ad letterpress. Squid beard brunch, exercitation raw denim yr sint direct trade. Raw denim narwhal id, flannel DIY McSweeney’s seitan. Letterpress artisan bespoke accusamus, meggings laboris consequat Truffaut qui in seitan. Sustainable cornhole Schlitz, twee Cosby sweater banh mi deep v forage letterpress flannel whatever keffiyeh. Sartorial cred irure, semiotics ethical sed blue bottle nihil letterpress.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Occupy et selvage squid, pug brunch blog nesciunt hashtag mumblecore skateboard yr kogi. Ugh small batch swag four loko. Fap post-ironic qui tote bag farm-to-table american apparel scenester keffiyeh vero, swag non pour-over gentrify authentic pitchfork. Schlitz scenester lo-fi voluptate, tote bag irony bicycle rights pariatur vero Vice freegan wayfarers exercitation nisi shoreditch. Chambray tofu vero sed. Street art swag literally leggings, Cosby sweater mixtape PBR lomo Banksy non in pitchfork ennui McSweeney’s selfies. Odd Future Banksy non authentic.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Aliquip enim artisan dolor post-ironic. Pug tote bag Marfa, deserunt pour-over Portland wolf eu odio intelligentsia american apparel ugh ea. Sunt viral et, 3 wolf moon gastropub pug id. Id fashion axe est typewriter, mlkshk Portland art party aute brunch. Sint pork belly Cosby sweater, deep v mumblecore kitsch american apparel. Try-hard direct trade tumblr sint skateboard. Adipisicing bitters excepteur biodiesel, pickled gastropub aute veniam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;footnotes&quot;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li id=&quot;fn-1&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Texture image courtesty of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.lovetextures.com/&quot;&gt;Lovetextures&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;#fnref-1&quot; class=&quot;footnote-backref&quot;&gt;↩&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sample Post]]></title><description><![CDATA[HTML Elements Below is just about everything you’ll need to style in the theme. Check the source code to see the many embedded elements…]]></description><link>https://juanosorio94.github.io/sample-post/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://juanosorio94.github.io/sample-post/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 07:26:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;HTML Elements&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is just about everything you’ll need to style in the theme. Check the source code to see the many embedded elements within paragraphs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Heading 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Heading 2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Heading 3&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Heading 4&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Heading 5&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;Heading 6&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Body text&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, test link adipiscing elit. &lt;strong&gt;This is strong&lt;/strong&gt;. Nullam dignissim convallis est. Quisque aliquam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1440635592348-167b1b30296f?crop=entropy&amp;#x26;dpr=2&amp;#x26;fit=crop&amp;#x26;fm=jpg&amp;#x26;h=475&amp;#x26;ixjsv=2.1.0&amp;#x26;ixlib=rb-0.3.5&amp;#x26;q=50&amp;#x26;w=1250&quot; alt=&quot;Smithsonian Image&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is emphasized&lt;/em&gt;. Donec faucibus. Nunc iaculis suscipit dui. 53 = 125. Water is H2O. Nam sit amet sem. Aliquam libero nisi, imperdiet at, tincidunt nec, gravida vehicula, nisl. The New York Times (That’s a citation). Underline.Maecenas ornare tortor. Donec sed tellus eget sapien fringilla nonummy. Mauris a ante. Suspendisse quam sem, consequat at, commodo vitae, feugiat in, nunc. Morbi imperdiet augue quis tellus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HTML and CSS are our tools. Mauris a ante. Suspendisse quam sem, consequat at, commodo vitae, feugiat in, nunc. Morbi imperdiet augue quis tellus. Praesent mattis, massa quis luctus fermentum, turpis mi volutpat justo, eu volutpat enim diam eget metus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Blockquotes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, test link adipiscing elit. Nullam dignissim convallis est. Quisque aliquam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Tables&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Header 1&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;Header 2&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;Header 3&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;cell 1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;cell 2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;cell 3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;cell 4&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;cell 5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;cell 6&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;List Types&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Ordered Lists&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Item one&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sub item one&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sub item two&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sub item three&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item two&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Unordered Lists&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item one&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item two&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item three&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sample Post]]></title><description><![CDATA[HTML Elements Below is just about everything you’ll need to style in the theme. Check the source code to see the many embedded elements…]]></description><link>https://juanosorio94.github.io/sample-post-2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://juanosorio94.github.io/sample-post-2/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 07:26:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;h2&gt;HTML Elements&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is just about everything you’ll need to style in the theme. Check the source code to see the many embedded elements within paragraphs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt;Heading 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Heading 2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Heading 3&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;Heading 4&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h5&gt;Heading 5&lt;/h5&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;Heading 6&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Body text&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, test link adipiscing elit. &lt;strong&gt;This is strong&lt;/strong&gt;. Nullam dignissim convallis est. Quisque aliquam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1440635592348-167b1b30296f?crop=entropy&amp;#x26;dpr=2&amp;#x26;fit=crop&amp;#x26;fm=jpg&amp;#x26;h=475&amp;#x26;ixjsv=2.1.0&amp;#x26;ixlib=rb-0.3.5&amp;#x26;q=50&amp;#x26;w=1250&quot; alt=&quot;Smithsonian Image&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is emphasized&lt;/em&gt;. Donec faucibus. Nunc iaculis suscipit dui. 53 = 125. Water is H2O. Nam sit amet sem. Aliquam libero nisi, imperdiet at, tincidunt nec, gravida vehicula, nisl. The New York Times (That’s a citation). Underline.Maecenas ornare tortor. Donec sed tellus eget sapien fringilla nonummy. Mauris a ante. Suspendisse quam sem, consequat at, commodo vitae, feugiat in, nunc. Morbi imperdiet augue quis tellus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;HTML and CSS are our tools. Mauris a ante. Suspendisse quam sem, consequat at, commodo vitae, feugiat in, nunc. Morbi imperdiet augue quis tellus. Praesent mattis, massa quis luctus fermentum, turpis mi volutpat justo, eu volutpat enim diam eget metus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Blockquotes&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, test link adipiscing elit. Nullam dignissim convallis est. Quisque aliquam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Tables&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
&lt;thead&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;Header 1&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;Header 2&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;th align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;Header 3&lt;/th&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/thead&gt;
&lt;tbody&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;cell 1&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;cell 2&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;cell 3&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;tr&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;left&quot;&gt;cell 4&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;cell 5&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;cell 6&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;/tr&gt;
&lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;List Types&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Ordered Lists&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Item one&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sub item one&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sub item two&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sub item three&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item two&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Unordered Lists&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item one&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item two&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Item three&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>